Opening Talk
Today's opening talk is given by Monami Yoshimura.
Yes, I will do my best.
It's been hot these days.
What about you, Ms. Natsu?
It was quite hot today.
I had a bit of a shock today,
I always like chocolate, and I always carry chocolate with me,
I always carry chocolate with me, but when I went to eat it earlier, it had already melted,
I couldn't eat it. Summer.
Really.
It's very harmful.
My gummies melt in the summer too,
So we are the same.
Yes, I had a string of about five gummy bears that melted.
That's right.
You should be careful, too.
So, Mr. Kodaira, I look forward to working with you.
It's hot, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
The chocolate melted.
I don't have any.
Earlier, I said it wasn't gummy either.
Well, can I start by leaning against the waterfall?
I can't. I can't. I can't.Impossible, impossible, impossible.
Chocolate?
No, I'm talking about chocolate.
Talking about melted chocolate?
Well, that's what we're going to talk about this time, isn't it?
This time, we'll be talking about Yugo Takanashi's Hot and Spicy Expedition Part 2!
Yugo Takanashi's Hot and Spicy Expedition Part 2!
Of course, you haven't seen the second part, have you, Mr. Sakuma?
No, I haven't.
That's why this time, too.
If there's anything you think is a little too much for Sakuma...
If there is something that you think is a little bit out of place, please stop me.
I see... I see.
I've seen it before.
It's the second time.
Well, I'll basically enjoy the VTR.
That's right.
Last time, even the staff couldn't remember the day.
I see.
So that's how it is.
After that recording, when we came out of the smoking area, we got together.
My lighter won't come on.
You're shaking.
So who did you say to me today?
He had a great reaction last time.Your reaction was so good last time.
Kimiku Fuisaki and
and Nichinichi no Meida, who struggled a little with her reaction last time.
I was with Meida, who had struggled with her reactions last time.
So it was just the three of us.
We were able to take advantage of what we learned from last time.
That's right.
I took notes of everything Sakuma-san said.
That's great.
We discussed with Meidan and Miki about what we should do.
We all three of us wanted to do this together.
I think we've grown up a little bit.
I think it's going to turn out in a way that no one could have predicted.
That's the best V you've ever done.
How do you like it now?
That wasn't so bad, was it?
That was the best V you've ever seen.
I'd like to see that.
It's great.
Yui Takanashi's second "Gekki-Hot Expedition.
Hey, you don't sound as good as you did in the first part.
So today's members are Miku Fujisaki and Meina Himino!
I'm so healed!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Almost by forceAlmost forced.
What does your T-shirt say?
You can do it.
My dad and friends saw it on YouTube.
I've been told to do my best.
I thought if I did it, I could be a good girl.
So, Meina-chan...
Why was I chosen?
We ate at the studio last time.
Let's eat.
It's not like Himino asked why I was chosen.
Don't decide if you want to play a character or not.
That's what makes it so hard for you, right?
I'll be careful.
Laugh out loud once?
Like Ghibli.
Like a Ghibli... from a famous restaurant to a very popular private store.
Takanashi's devil's advocate is wonderful.
It's so good!
The rocket is so important!
Oil soba, oni?
Wow! This is spicy!
Yeah, there's a really cute picture next to this place.
It's cute. It's delicious.
It's delicious.Yeah...
The introduction of the store may not have been edited in time, but I think the signboard is a bit clunky.
I think that even if you show it as a narration base, you might think that the bread on the signboard would be enough.
Let's continue.
You want a cigarette?
Let's go, go, go, go.
Next, continue.
There's a really cute picture next to the cat store.
Cute?
Like, it looks good?
Yeah, it looks great.
It's not gonna look good.
It's too scary.
It's the scariest demon I've ever seen.
This is a real book of demons.
Your hands... they're starting to look like peppers.
Matching nails.
Member colors.
That's great.
My hands... they're getting peppery.
It's almost me.
What?
What? Oh, I see.
Cute!
Try it!Try it!
Curious? I like it!
Wow!
It's a reaction!
A cessor human being...
I will never let you go
sort of
There's a pattern like that.
Good morning.
I'm sufra.
Pleased to meet you.
Thanks to our customers.
Even at the oil soba restaurant.
Thank you very much.
I'm tired of this guy over here.
This is Akaoni Soba.
There's a special.
He's having trouble breathing.
I worry that I'll start to lose my breath.
Very spicy, very spicy, very spicy.
Do you want to pay extra to make it spicy?
No, I don't eat regular.
You eat regular.
It's okay.I'm okay with this.
Let's stop for a second.
We need to show them what's on the menu.
I don't know what's on the menu.
I don't know what's bothering you.
We need to organize the information here.
You're right.
I don't even know what it says.
That's one layer.
It's better to just cut it off and put it in a still picture.
It's better to stop there.
You should be careful about that.
You should be polite about it.
You didn't have time, did you?
Hey, from the location to the edit.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
This is amazing.
First look.
Three of us, please.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Why are you wearing costumes?
Last time, I wore a sunflower costume.
I was on location.I had the opportunity to shoot on location.
Me and Ryoka-chan went
over to the back.
It was for a costume, so
I'm now in plain clothes.
Wait a minute.
Can we go back for a second?
Can we get a three-shot?
Fujisaki, don't you have a TV face?
Not your idol face?
It's not the time for that!
But it's still very interesting, isn't it?
What I really dislike is the style.
So you're okay with this?
I've been getting a lot of calls right after the show went on the air.
Oh, that's right!
Yui, I knew you could eat so much from the moon.
But I didn't expect it to go this far.
Very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very...
No, it just looks delicious.
I can drink it pretty strong.
Looks delicious
It has a lot of spices in it.
I think it's a little bit different from what I've had before
I'm not sure if I can eat itI'm a little skeptical about being able to eat it.
Next time
Looks bad, looks bad, looks bad!
Iniguri Ramen
Is this ramen?
Wow!
Bon appétit. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Wow!
Wow, that looks delicious.
How do you do it?
You can smell it. It smells so good.
What?
Fujisaki.
Fujisaki's amazing.
Can I see your face one more time?
It's so good.
It's like something out of a flask.
It's like a hockey stick.
How did you get it to fly?
It's not so bad this far
It's kind of funny. It's totally funny
No, I sure don't like this.
It smells really good.You smell really good.
No, no, no, I can smell it already. I can smell it.
It's like a spicy chili pepper or mara spice.
There's a cheese savior for Meira and Mikkun.
It's a little bit of cheese.
It's a secret.
Yui Takanashi's second "super spicy" expedition!
Let's get ready to eat!
Bon appétit!
Mix it all together!
Your face is so hot!
I got a shot of him just now.
The way he said it's a secret...
That's right.
It's not like there's too much going on.
It's really a book about what happens next, right?
It's a little different when you do it that way.
You've been doing that a lot today.
Look at your face.
Let's go.
I think I just saw something I shouldn't have.
What is it? What do you want to see?
It's all over the noodles.
It's so red.
Why do you say that's cool?Why are you saying it's cool?
You've got to get this thing involved.
This is so bad.
This is so fucked up.
I hope it's okay.
Looks delicious.
That's a lot of food.
It'll be great.
That's it. That's it.
You okay? - Yeah.
Go, go, go, go.
Are you okay?
You can never be okay.
Like a little bit of that lozenge.
Rub it, is that okay?
Oh, my God.
Something's wrong with Leo's face.
That's Leora's face.
I love it.
I don't know what you're saying, but...
I'm scared.
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
Are you okay?
Your reaction was a little worrisome.The reaction was on a slightly worrisome level.
I'm not expecting it, but I'm letting it creep up on me.
No way.
Happy Birthday!
Scary in more ways than one.
Are you sweating? Are you nervous? Are you okay?
I'm so nervous.
Okay, hold my hand.
Bon appétit.
Go for it, Mena.
I'm scared.
I'm going to go now.
Why?
Oh, is it hard?
Aah! Bwe, bwe, bwe, bwe, bwe, bwe.
Buhe-buh-buh-buh-buh.
Is he gone?
Really?
They're gone!
Gone?
What do you mean, "I'm gonna lose my throat"?
That's a rare expression.
Come on, Fuji saikis, help him more.
You know the pain. Help him.
Maybe he's not on the same level as last time.Maybe the level is different from last time.
I hope it's okay.
Oh, wait, I'm getting really scared.
Oh my God, wait, I'm scared.
On a scale of one to ten, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion, ten billion.
Wait, the air feels a hundred times heavier than last time.
Oh, that hurts!
Wait, I'm scared, but I'll mix it!
I'll mix it up!
Smile, smile, smile!
You've lost your touch, haven't you?
I'll be back later.
Delicious!
Oh, no.
You don't want some?
Oh, I'm glad.
But it's the spiciest thing I've ever eaten.
It's delicious! It's so good!
Amazing.
This...
Holocaust.
Why are you talking?
I can't feel a thing.
Oh, wait, that's painful.
It's painful.Wait, it's hot, it's hot, it's hot
Oh, it's painful.
Suddenly?
I'm glad.
I'm glad you found something spicy.
Cheer up.
I'm surprised you can go through with it.
I'm amazed you can eat this much.
It's delicious.
Try it!
This is the first time I've had spicy food like this!
Oh my god, it's so spicy!
Oh no, it's so spicy!
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
We had a strategy meeting.
Seriously?
Oh, man, it's really spicy.
If I drink water, it'll be even worse.
It makes me want to drink. I can't take it anymore.
"Chief, is this something we should eat against? I said...
I don't think so.
Impossible?
Have you ever had one before?
Maybe two?
Maybe two?Maybe two?
I've never had a drink before.
How long?
How many years?
Only two years.
Who are you? Did you prepare this?
Captain?
It's a little spicy.
It's hot.
I can feel it.
I've never felt it before in my life.
Pre-press-me-borial.
Oh!
I was just wondering if the spice would fly away a little bit.
Maybe I'm being a little silly.
Really.
I don't think I'd drink alcohol if it was really spicy.
I'm scared.
Scary.
Wow, how can it hurt?
It's like you don't wear lipstick.
It's gonna hurt.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm. - Mm-hm.Mm-hmm.
Wow.
That's some guts for a giraffe.
Bon appétit.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Yay.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
I have feelings.
Can I just say something really captain-like up there?
Yeah, sure.
This is getting a little out of hand.
What do you think, Miku?
Captain.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Captain.
Mik-chan, it says so much in the teaser, all at once.
She can do it!
Let's go!Let's go!
Wow, you're going well.
That's great.
You're doing great. - I'm done.
That was amazing. That went really well.
He doesn't bite anymore.
I'm impressed.
You can drink that?
No more bites.
Isn't it great?
That's great.
What? - Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
That's not good.
Is this really from an abura soba shop?
This is not from a noodle shop.
This is classy.
Stand lady!
Mr. Sakuma, please give me a location too!
I'll be in my position for a while.
This is not a gourmet food show
This is not that cute video.
No, but you're showing your guts.No, but he's showing his guts.
This is great.
Take it easy.
No, I'm responsible for taking them both here.
That's great.
Meina and Miki did their best.
I'll go in the name of the captain, too.
I'm off!
Bon appétit!
Wow!
Amazing!
Amazing.
Wow. Oh, man.
So much.
Oh, wow.
Wow! Wow, wow!
We're gonna eat like TV champions.
I can't feel it anymore.
Mmm, yummy!
Are you kidding me?
Now, we're all working hard.
But it's spicy.
It's very satisfying.
This is kind of fun to watch.
Oh, it's spicy, spicy, spicy. It's delicious.Oh, spicy, spicy, spicy, delicious!
Oh!
I got it!
It's here!
Hmmm....Nobi?
For a moment, I think I'll stop this one then. This is not bad at all.
But if you don't explain how far you've eaten, you won't be able to see how hard Takanashi is working.
It would be better to know how much he has eaten.
It would be good if it reaches this state. What percentage?
We want that information to be shared, don't we?
That's really true.
I almost forgot.
That's OK!
Sometimes people forget.
I'll just keep looking.
I'm afraid to go next time.
Blade of Death
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
Oh, no.
I fucked someone.
I'm Mr. Schloss Klaustreich.
Wow, wow, nice to meet you.
I'm sorry! Wait a minute!
I'm scared, I'm scared!
Oh no, it's stimulating your brain too!Oh, no, it's stimulating your brain, too.
Like, suddenly it wants to fly.
It's interesting to see it go this far.
It's funny when it gets this far.
You've got talent like this.
It's so real, Naracer.
It's so real.
Oh, no, it's stimulating your brain.
I'm going crazy.
That hurts.
That's a lot, isn't it?
You're crying.
Don't cry.
It's so good, I don't want to eat it.
It's not what you said.
It's delicious.
I don't want to eat it.
No, I won't.
It's good.
It's so cute.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm scared.
Why did you bring him here?
Al.
I'm scared.I'm scared.
You said the other day you were scared and you said you never thought it would be hard.
It's hard.
Failure.
I can't fail.
You're on the wrong side of the table.
She's sobbing her eyes out.
Ruin must've brought us here.
Captain.
What?
Oh no!
What the hell?
That was so...
That was painful.
It was so hard.
Oh, Gibberish!
It's so hard.
I thought you said you loved kekikara.
But today...
I feel sorry for you. I don't do rituras.
I couldn't eat today.
I'm sorry.
But it was delicious.
Please do the third one, Sakuma-san!
Just a little.A little bit.
I'd like you to do this for me.
Is it good?
It's delicious!
Thank you for the food!
Yes! Great!
That was fun!
It was a bit of a giveaway, though,
How was it for you, Takei?
From Takei's point of view, it was a lot of fun!
It was fun! There was a lot of drama,
And the T-shirt came back to life at the end.
It came back alive.
It was wonderful!
Each of the three of them had their own special charms, so it was a good reason.
How was it, Takanashi?
I cried so hard that I remember watching it.
That's how hard it was!
But I learned a lot,
I felt like I could share my feelings with everyone for the first time,
I felt like I was able to grow as a person. As a person.
How was Hibi?
Well, it was very painful,
Yui will cry too.Yui will cry now.
The mix is broken.
We were caught in the middle and our positions were reversed,
I didn't know what to do anymore.
But a new side of Fujisaki came out.
He was in such a bad way.
It was bad.
Really.
It was so hard that I had to take a cab for a 10-minute walk.
It was so hard that I couldn't walk.
I see.
That's amazing.
That's how hard it was.
I heard that the staff had a little bit of a chat with you.
I don't know what the unit of severity is.
Actually, there is a color meter to standardize it.
The maximum is 5, but the restaurant I just visited has a 4.8 color meter.
The human limit is 5.
The one that is ranked about 20th in the nation's spicy food ranking.
The last one was exactly 4 color meters.
The last one, Maboku, is about 670th.
I ate spicy food to the human limit.
See, if you think of it as a shonen manga, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Once Vegeta's.Once Vegeta's.
Roll it up.
Like this, save and save.
We're going to do it so that we can get revenge on that place, right?
After the 10th meeting, we'll go back there again.
What kind of restaurant?
Fujisaki's.
Why me?
What else do you dislike, Fujisaki?
What's your pet peeve? Screaming.
Screaming?
Screaming scares me.
We've just decided on a location.
The one I asked for.
I wanted to ask for the Mother Farm location.
Screaming. It's a scream, isn't it?
I'll do it. I finally did it.
Next time preview
Thank you for watching until the end. This time it's a dog version!
Ready, go!